GOUTAM KUMAR RAY

Fresher(teacher)

Delhi, Delhi

gkrarunray@gmail.com

7779859035

I am teaching 4 year and 5 year study in commerce, company, marketing, management, I am stay foolish stay hungry for knowledge/experience. I am optimist, hardworking, and focus of my work /duty/goal. Thank you

Willing to relocate to: Mukerjee Nagar, Delhi - North delhi - Delhi, Delhi



WORK EXPERIENCE

Basic computer

Gurukul computer academy - Hazaribag, Jharkhand September 2018 to November 2019

Basic knowledge of computer hardware and software. MS OFFICE,MS WORD,MS POWERPOINT etc

Home tutions

Under 10 th - Hazaribag, Jharkhand August 2017 to August 2019

To 10 th 9 th level student teach case student

Teacher of commerce

Sri sai commerce academy - Hazaribag, Jharkhand April 2016 to August 2018

Lteach icom and bcom student



EDUCATION

Knowledge about india and world in Civil service

Bhumi ias - Delhi, Delhi November 2019 to August 2020

Bachelors in Bechlor in commerce (company,tax, management,account,marketing etc)

Vinoba bhave university hazaribag - Hazaribag, Jharkhand April 2015 to August 2018

Higher Secondary(12th Pass) in (I.COM)Business study,English, business mathematics, entrepreneurship, accountancy

Markham college of commerce hazaribag - Hazaribag, Jharkhand

Secondary(10th Pass) in English hindi science math social science

Utkarmit high school chitrokurha - Giridih, Jharkhand April 2012 to April 2013



My home village dhanukdih, giridih, jharkhand. I finding good thing in each and every bad circumstances..